<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yujia Lyu</title>
    <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://YujiaLyu.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Yujia Lyu</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/media/icon_hu65a915bb538585c232735a818d34e461_39321_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Yujia Lyu</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Psychology and Organizations</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/publication/social_psych_org/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/publication/social_psych_org/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sentiments and Status: The Dyad? The Triad? Or Both?</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/publication/sentiment_triad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/publication/sentiment_triad/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Competence or Dominance?: A Quasi-Experimental Test of Sense of Control, Status and Power</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/publication/control_status/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/publication/control_status/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Film Review: Cults and Extreme Belief</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/publication/teach_review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/publication/teach_review/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micro-Level Production of Durable Inequality -- A Status Diffusion Approach</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/project/status_diffusion_role/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/project/status_diffusion_role/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style =&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tilly (1998) theorized that persistent inequality between social categories emerge when categorical distinctions are mapped onto organizational hierarchies (e.g., male manager versus female Assistant). Routine practices from the organizational role hierarchies make categorical distinctions hard to replace. Previous research has yet to thoroughly delineate the mechanism. The current study, drawing from status diffusion theories (Berger and Fişek 2006; Ridgeway 1991), propose and test a status process that makes categorical inequality endure. Using a modified status construction experiment (Ridgeway et al. 1998), I systematically examine whether role hierarchies are sufficient in making arbitrary categorical distinctions differentiated in perceived status and competence. Results show that the categorical membership consistently associated with a superior role was widely perceived as having higher status. Yet, participants did not develop stereotypes differentiating the two group in competence. The study also shows that different exposures to the role hierarchy affect status diffusion. Future implications and limitations are discussed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;color: grey&#34;&gt;ASA Social Psychology Graduate Student Investigator Award (honorable mention)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;color: grey&#34;&gt;2023 60th Midwest Sociological Society Graduate Student Paper Competition Award (First Place)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;color: grey&#34;&gt;Currently under review at Social Psychology Quarterly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Structural Social Psychology - Micro-level Interactions and Inequality</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/talk/structural-social-psychology-micro-level-interactions-and-inequality/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/talk/structural-social-psychology-micro-level-interactions-and-inequality/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;虽然研究社会心理学的学者不少，但是社会心理学似乎在社会学界显得有些默默无闻，尤其是结构社会心理学这一分支。这个从观察小组活动出发的实验社会学分支其实为我们了解宏观的结构文化与个体如何互相影响提供了非常多的视角和理论，也为研究社会不平等的产生和维系提供了很多思路。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这次，来和大家聊一聊社会学家怎么关注微观世界？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;本次讲座将分享三个部分：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;结构社会心理学（structural social psychology）研究什么？&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;微观的互动如何加固或重塑我们熟知的文化规范和认知模式，维系不平等？&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;结构社会心理学去哪里学？到哪里找？学了干什么？&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status and Power in Interactive Service Work</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/project/status_service/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/project/status_service/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style =&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How do workers consent to their self-exploitation and stay in unequal labor relations? This is a classic question in the study of workplace inequality, with many researchers dedicated to identify the underlying mechanisms. Borrowing insights from structural social psychological theories, this paper explicates how experimental research about micro-level status and exchange processes contribute to the study of inequality reproduction at work. Psychological outcomes during workplace encounters worth a thorough assessment. I further discuss how a mixed-method approach could faciliate research investigating beliefs, emotions, and behavioral patterns arising from workplace interactions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exposure to Workplace Hierarchy and Leadership among Working Students</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/project/working_student/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/project/working_student/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style =&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;project-background&#34;&gt;Project Background:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the third empirical chapter of my dissertation, which investigates working student’s experience with workplace hierarchy and leadership. I interviewed students at the University of Iowa with work experiences. The project aims to explore how exposure to hierarchies at work relates to students’ conceptualization of ideal leaders and their engagement in leadership opportunities on campus. By examining reactions to hierarchies in natural settings, this work allows me to identify factors that may disrupt the reproduction of status or power hierarchies, therefore advancing our knowledge about consequences of hierarchies. I am currently conducting analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Triadic Standard Experimental Setting</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/project/three_person_experiment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/project/three_person_experiment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style =&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;color: grey&#34;&gt;With Alison Bianchi and Inga Popovaite&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;project-background&#34;&gt;Project Background:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using python, we have constructed a experimental protocol allowing participants to interact with two other people and develop status hierarchy within the small group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facing Multifaceted Racism against Asian, What Can We Do?</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/talk/facing-multifaceted-racism-against-asian-what-can-we-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/talk/facing-multifaceted-racism-against-asian-what-can-we-do/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;从美国前总统的种族主义污言，如“中国病毒”，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;到最近美国亚特兰大按摩店的八人被枪杀事件，包括六名亚裔女性。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;你以为歧视离你很远？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;实际上每个人都可能是偏见的受害者。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;微信公众号“Sociological理论大缸” 在本周日（4月18日）举办线上分享讲座：遭遇多面的亚裔歧视，我们能做些什么。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maintenance of Polarized (Dis)Trust--Science Skepticism in Covid-19 Mask Debate</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/project/mask_in_media/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/project/mask_in_media/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style =&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;color: grey&#34;&gt;With Michael Sauder and Mario A. Paez-Arellano&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;project-description&#34;&gt;Project Description:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is currently a stark political divide in trust in science in the United States, a divide that emerged in the 1970s and has been growing over time (Gauchat 2012; 2015; maybe check on current state of this). While the origins of this polarization have been debated, there is little empirical work on how trust in scientific insights and scientists became politicized. We know even less about the processes through which this politicization is maintained and revitalized over time. How do people lose trust in institutions? How is this loss of trust sustained over time?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We attempt to develop a better understanding of the answers to these questions by carefully examining a key pathway through which trust is eroded: the promotion of skepticism. Specifically, we analyze how skepticism is expressed in popular news media, concentrating on the different ways in which various media outlets created and perpetuated skepticism about the use of facemasks during the first year of the COVID-19 pandemic. By closely examining how news outlets with different political identities express skepticism in a time of acute scientific uncertainty, we gain focused insight into how skepticism is raised, the different forms skepticism takes, and how skepticism is (in some cases) resolved. While all of our news sources expressed skepticism about scientific experts during this time period, there are striking differences in the frequency, endurance, and nature of skepticism across the political spectrum. These differences in how skepticism is constructed in various media shed light on one important dynamic that contributes to politically polarized trust in science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discourse of Control in Newspaper (1979-2019)</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/project/control_in_media/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/project/control_in_media/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style =&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;project-background&#34;&gt;Project Background:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Demonstrating strong control over one’s own life is morally encouraged and sometimes required by American society. Potent as this tenet shapes individual behaviors, it can only remain strong through repeated instantiations in our daily lives. To understand how the value of having control is woven into American’s mainstream individualistic culture, I explore its manifestation in one of the major conduits for conveying social values (albeit its diminishing influence these days) – newspapers. For this project, I gathered 3669 newspaper articles published in the U.S. from 1979 to 2020 that include the phrase “sense of control” through Next Uni (previously known as LexisNexis Academic). By conducting text and network analysis, I will first examine different life aspects or topics associated with the discussion of control, as well as their variation along the time (what aspects or topics become increasingly/decreasingly/no long related to “sense of control”?). Additionally, the usage of the phrase will be examined syntactically to gauge the ways in which different social actors engage with the concept to act on the object of interest, and semantically to explore the attitudinal aspects correlate with the phrase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;project-objectives&#34;&gt;Project Objectives:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore topics associated with the “control” discourse by time periods:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate text co-occurrence network by time periods and detect the network community structure to extract topics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visualize the proportion of texts devoted to each topic by time to demonstrate the topics’ variation in significance related to control as time flows (e.g. Rule et al. 2015).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Investigate the usage of the phrase “sense of control” to detect the major-patterns people use it in navigating through their lives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understand Ourselves in the Pandemic - A Social Psychological Perspective</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/talk/understand-ourselves-in-the-pandemic-a-social-psychological-perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/talk/understand-ourselves-in-the-pandemic-a-social-psychological-perspective/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;一场疫情，将人们熟悉的生活场景和生活方式悉数打碎。我们的个人境遇也陷入了极大的不确定之中。国内疫情的逐渐缓和，我们的反思尚未止步——经历破碎之后的创伤、有待平缓的情绪安慰。同时，国际环境又风波不断——从民族主义到集体歧视。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;本次讲座面向社会心理学爱好者和研究者，分享情感规则、社会认同和情感控制三大方面的社会心理学理论，探讨它们对疫情中个体挣扎、群际事件、集体反应提供的启发和研究思路。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;本讲座是微信公众号“Sociological理论大缸”的月初讲座系列No.3。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/slides/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/slides/example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;create-slides-in-markdown-with-wowchemy&#34;&gt;Create slides in Markdown with Wowchemy&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Wowchemy&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&#34;https://owchemy.com/docs/managing-content/#create-slides&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Efficiently write slides in Markdown&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-in-1: Create, Present, and Publish your slides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports speaker notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile friendly slides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;controls&#34;&gt;Controls&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next: &lt;code&gt;Right Arrow&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;Space&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous: &lt;code&gt;Left Arrow&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start: &lt;code&gt;Home&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finish: &lt;code&gt;End&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overview: &lt;code&gt;Esc&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speaker notes: &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fullscreen: &lt;code&gt;F&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zoom: &lt;code&gt;Alt + Click&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/hakimel/reveal.js#pdf-export&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;PDF Export&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;code&gt;E&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;code-highlighting&#34;&gt;Code Highlighting&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inline code: &lt;code&gt;variable&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Code block:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-python&#34;&gt;porridge = &amp;quot;blueberry&amp;quot;
if porridge == &amp;quot;blueberry&amp;quot;:
    print(&amp;quot;Eating...&amp;quot;)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;math&#34;&gt;Math&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In-line math: $x + y = z$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Block math:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
f\left( x \right) = ;\frac{{2\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x - 4} \right)}}{{\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x + 1} \right)}}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;fragments&#34;&gt;Fragments&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make content appear incrementally&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{% fragment %}} One {{% /fragment %}}
{{% fragment %}} **Two** {{% /fragment %}}
{{% fragment %}} Three {{% /fragment %}}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Press &lt;code&gt;Space&lt;/code&gt; to play!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
One
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Two&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
Three
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A fragment can accept two optional parameters:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;class&lt;/code&gt;: use a custom style (requires definition in custom CSS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;weight&lt;/code&gt;: sets the order in which a fragment appears&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;speaker-notes&#34;&gt;Speaker Notes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Add speaker notes to your presentation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34;&gt;{{% speaker_note %}}
- Only the speaker can read these notes
- Press `S` key to view
{{% /speaker_note %}}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Press the &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt; key to view the speaker notes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;aside class=&#34;notes&#34;&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only the speaker can read these notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt; key to view&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;/aside&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;themes&#34;&gt;Themes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;black: Black background, white text, blue links (default)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;white: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;league: Gray background, white text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;beige: Beige background, dark text, brown links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sky: Blue background, thin dark text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;night: Black background, thick white text, orange links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;serif: Cappuccino background, gray text, brown links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;simple: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;solarized: Cream-colored background, dark green text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;section data-noprocess data-shortcode-slide
  
      
      data-background-image=&#34;/media/boards.jpg&#34;
  &gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;custom-slide&#34;&gt;Custom Slide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Customize the slide style and background&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34;&gt;{{&amp;lt; slide background-image=&amp;quot;/media/boards.jpg&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
{{&amp;lt; slide background-color=&amp;quot;#0000FF&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
{{&amp;lt; slide class=&amp;quot;my-style&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;custom-css-example&#34;&gt;Custom CSS Example&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s make headers navy colored.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create &lt;code&gt;assets/css/reveal_custom.css&lt;/code&gt; with:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-css&#34;&gt;.reveal section h1,
.reveal section h2,
.reveal section h3 {
  color: navy;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;questions&#34;&gt;Questions?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-modules/discussions&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Ask&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/managing-content/#create-slides&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>University of Iowa Parental Leave Survey Report</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/public_report/parental_leave/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/public_report/parental_leave/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Report can be found here: (&lt;a href=&#34;https://ppc.uiowa.edu/publications/university-iowa-parental-leave-survey-report%29&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://ppc.uiowa.edu/publications/university-iowa-parental-leave-survey-report)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading with Yujia</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/talk/reading-with-yujia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/talk/reading-with-yujia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my personal blog documenting and sharing interesting research in social psychology, social stratification, and inequality to Chinese audiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;记录社会心理学，社会分层和不平等的有趣研究。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find the website here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.zhihu.com/column/xiaoyutan&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://www.zhihu.com/column/xiaoyutan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/admin/config.yml</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/admin/config.yml</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/skills/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
