<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Content Analysis | Yujia Lyu</title>
    <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/tag/content-analysis/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://YujiaLyu.github.io/tag/content-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Content Analysis</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/media/icon_hu65a915bb538585c232735a818d34e461_39321_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Content Analysis</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/tag/content-analysis/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maintenance of Polarized (Dis)Trust--Science Skepticism in Covid-19 Mask Debate</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/project/mask_in_media/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/project/mask_in_media/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style =&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;color: grey&#34;&gt;With Michael Sauder and Mario A. Paez-Arellano&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;project-description&#34;&gt;Project Description:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is currently a stark political divide in trust in science in the United States, a divide that emerged in the 1970s and has been growing over time (Gauchat 2012; 2015; maybe check on current state of this). While the origins of this polarization have been debated, there is little empirical work on how trust in scientific insights and scientists became politicized. We know even less about the processes through which this politicization is maintained and revitalized over time. How do people lose trust in institutions? How is this loss of trust sustained over time?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We attempt to develop a better understanding of the answers to these questions by carefully examining a key pathway through which trust is eroded: the promotion of skepticism. Specifically, we analyze how skepticism is expressed in popular news media, concentrating on the different ways in which various media outlets created and perpetuated skepticism about the use of facemasks during the first year of the COVID-19 pandemic. By closely examining how news outlets with different political identities express skepticism in a time of acute scientific uncertainty, we gain focused insight into how skepticism is raised, the different forms skepticism takes, and how skepticism is (in some cases) resolved. While all of our news sources expressed skepticism about scientific experts during this time period, there are striking differences in the frequency, endurance, and nature of skepticism across the political spectrum. These differences in how skepticism is constructed in various media shed light on one important dynamic that contributes to politically polarized trust in science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discourse of Control in Newspaper (1979-2019)</title>
      <link>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/project/control_in_media/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://YujiaLyu.github.io/project/control_in_media/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style =&#34;text-align: left&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;project-background&#34;&gt;Project Background:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Demonstrating strong control over one’s own life is morally encouraged and sometimes required by American society. Potent as this tenet shapes individual behaviors, it can only remain strong through repeated instantiations in our daily lives. To understand how the value of having control is woven into American’s mainstream individualistic culture, I explore its manifestation in one of the major conduits for conveying social values (albeit its diminishing influence these days) – newspapers. For this project, I gathered 3669 newspaper articles published in the U.S. from 1979 to 2020 that include the phrase “sense of control” through Next Uni (previously known as LexisNexis Academic). By conducting text and network analysis, I will first examine different life aspects or topics associated with the discussion of control, as well as their variation along the time (what aspects or topics become increasingly/decreasingly/no long related to “sense of control”?). Additionally, the usage of the phrase will be examined syntactically to gauge the ways in which different social actors engage with the concept to act on the object of interest, and semantically to explore the attitudinal aspects correlate with the phrase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;project-objectives&#34;&gt;Project Objectives:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore topics associated with the “control” discourse by time periods:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate text co-occurrence network by time periods and detect the network community structure to extract topics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visualize the proportion of texts devoted to each topic by time to demonstrate the topics’ variation in significance related to control as time flows (e.g. Rule et al. 2015).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Investigate the usage of the phrase “sense of control” to detect the major-patterns people use it in navigating through their lives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
